S: Can I help you?
B: Yes. Do you have these in an eleven?
S: Just a minute. I’ll go and check.
B: Thank you.
S: Here you are.
These are an eleven. Do you want to try them on?
B: No, thanks. I’m sure they’ll be fine.
S: That will be eighty pounds.
B: Oh, it says ninety-five ninety-nine.
S: Yes, they’re on sale.
B: Oh. Great!
Thank you.
S: Thank you.
B: Bye.
S: Bye bye, now.
S: Can I help you?
B: Yes, I just bought these.
S: I remember.
Is there a problem?
B: Yes, they’re too big.
S: What size are they?
B: They’re an eleven. I take a US eleven.
S: Oh, right.
American sizes are always one size larger.
You need a UK ten. Just a minute…
I’m sorry, but we don’t have those in a ten.
But we do have these and they’re the same price, or you can have a refund.
B: I’ll take this pair, then.
S: Oh, do you have the receipt?
B: Sure.
Here you go.
S: Great.
B: Thank you.